<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Yens Loff</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Yens Loff</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 10:29:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Go Module Mirror Supply Chain Attack</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/go-module-mirror-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 10:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/go-module-mirror-attack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the world of software development, security is a paramount concern, especially as developers increasingly rely on third-party packages to build their applications. A recent incident concerning the Go programming language&amp;rsquo;s module mirror has highlighted the vulnerabilities inherent in relying on these external packages. This article delves into that incident, exploring supply chain attacks, the mechanisms behind them, and what developers can do to safeguard their code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happened&#34;&gt;What Happened?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more than three years, &lt;mark&gt;the Go module mirror served malicious packages that exploited developer trust.&lt;/mark&gt; Researchers identified these unsafe modifications in the supply chain, pointing to a critical weakness in how programmers use package managers. This incident underscores a significant issue faced by users of many modern programming languages, including Go, Python, and JavaScript: the risk of unvetted third-party code infiltrating software projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Latest Rsync Vulnerability: A 2025 Breakdown of Buffer Overflows</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/rsync-exploit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 12:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/rsync-exploit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In 2025, the discovery of a high-severity vulnerability in Rsync—a pivotal open-source software for remote file synchronization—serves as a sobering reminder of the persistent security challenges in the software development community. This vulnerability, classified as a CVE with a &lt;mark&gt;severity rating of 9.8&lt;/mark&gt;, underscores the fact that despite advancements in technology and security practices, fundamental issues like buffer overflows continue to plague even the most beloved software.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-rsync&#34;&gt;What is Rsync?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rsync is a widely respected protocol that streamlines the process of synchronizing files between a client and a server. Its efficiency is largely due to a unique mechanism that allows it to only transfer changed portions of files rather than the entire file. This method helps save both time and bandwidth, making Rsync a popular choice for managing and backing up files.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposed: The Apps That Leak Your Location and Your Privacy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/apps-leak-location/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/apps-leak-location/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, our privacy is at constant risk, and recent revelations about apps leaking location data add a new layer of concern. A hacking breach has brought to light the unsettling truth about how certain apps can inadvertently expose our movements to law enforcement and data brokers alike. This article delves into these alarming findings, highlighting key incidents from prominent platforms like Gravy Analytics, Telegram, and even Apple’s Siri, ultimately raising questions about our digital safety and privacy rights.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
